[{"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Specifically, apparently, so you can you vote for Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Five-year break.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Mickey, how are you?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "The acting wasn't something I was having fun doing anymore or liked doing.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "I've always wondered, why would you -- in the middle of this dazzling film career -- want to go and get beaten around the head?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "You've always loved boxing, haven't you?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "It went good.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "How did it go, the boxing?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I never say could have, would have, should have.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Did you ever think you could have been a proper contestant?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "You know what it was, I needed the discipline.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "But what does it give you, that feeling when you get into the ring?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I did the movie at a time when I still wasn't very bankable.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "And, boy, was it the comeback movie?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the guy did a really great job with the nose.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I always had trouble with wrapping my hands, because my hands would swell up.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Is that from the fighting?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Well, I did it because I had some issues when I was very young with authority and with physical --", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why do you think you did it?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "It was terrible.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "In the wilderness years, I mean, when you were walking, say, into a store in Hollywood, a grocery store or something, what was the reality of that?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, didn't you used to be.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "You actually hear that line?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I'm not going to go there.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "ORGAN: What was the worst name?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Well, Stallone helped me out.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Who were the guys, the other actors who really stuck by you?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Had you seen each other since?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "It's always nerve-racking.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "When you met up again this time, how did it go?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Well, the first time we saw each in over 20 years was last year or something.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Or was it weary?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I don't have any desire to read it.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "What was your view of the book?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "No, but I -- I mean, it's fascinating, because I have discussed this with you before.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Anyway, what's the next thing you want to talk about?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "No, I don't have to wonder.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Do you ever wonder about that?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I think I'm feeling you, Mickey.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "You feel me?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "No, they're stronger than us.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Do you understand them better?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "It would be a terrible place.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Hey, listen, it would be a really terrible place if it was just me, you and these camera guys, you know?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "No, I'm -- to date, not necessarily, no.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Are an easier guy to go out with, to date, to be with?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Listen, when I -- listen, just to get the second chance, they're letting me back in the door.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Is that the ultimate?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Do you still feel that?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "It wasn't the drinking.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Do you still drink much?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "My anger.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What was your problem?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "And does that still flare up?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Now that he has seen your face, he knows.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Does he know he butchered my mother?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "OURKE: Yes, he did.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "He came out to your premier last week?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "You told me.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Who told you?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "I have -- I like the way you say with your country.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "What do you make of what's happening with your country right now?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "I don't really have one, to be honest with you.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "What is going wrong with America?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Are you learning a bit of diplomatic tact in your old age, Mickey?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I'll let you read my mind.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Do you think actors should spout off about politics?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "No, I didn't get engaged.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "There's a wild rumor you got engaged recently?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "None of your business, Piers.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Are you with anyone in any sort of serious way?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "You're quite bossy, aren't you?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "But you see, you did it.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Do you always get your own way?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "He's big, but he's very gentle.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "I mean, you boss him around?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have met Seal?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Four.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Because it felt like the pair of you had been sort of searching for each other and then you collided, and you have this extraordinary life with hundreds of children and fabulously successful careers?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Was it really?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I was just visiting a friend.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "What were you both doing there?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I hadn't met him before.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "You knew him, right?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Then we met each other again, but always with friends.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "So what happened then?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "It went like this and normally we'd go and we just went like this.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do you want to go through it again (ph)?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "We both gripped each other.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "And who gripped who?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I got really hot.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "And what were you thinking in that second?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I was like, oh, wow.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Did you think this is the guy?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Had you kissed lots of frogs to get to this point?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "So you squeeze hands, and then you get married.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Otherwise, things just don't get done, do they?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "He had an igloo built on a mountain?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "\"Do you want to marry me?\"", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "And what were his exact words of proposal?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I said yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "And then nine months later Henry was born.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "ORGAN: And then what happened?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know how that happened.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "How do you be a mother to four children with everything else you do?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "No, that's it.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Are there any more planned?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Do you like working with him?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "How do you keep this skinny figure that you have?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "No way.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you started it there would be nine seasons?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "-- right?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Did I pronounce that right?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Was that always the dream for you?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "You conquered the world of modeling, didn't you?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "For this industry, yes, because the designers such as him, they require the girls to be a certain weight, height and size.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 771, "question": "Not thin enough and too short?", "qSentId": 770}, {"answer": "I mean, I --", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "And, also, it's dangerous sort of nonsense that he's spouting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "I mean, there is a danger --", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "If I don't, I go back to Germany and I do something else, you know?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "Any -- any scalpel at any stage?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "I mean, I don't want to say never.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 818, "question": "Would you ever?", "qSentId": 817}, {"answer": "That, too.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "You like making money, don't you?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "I don't know if I'm that smart at it.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 872, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 871}, {"answer": "I've been here since '94.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "-- keen to do that?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "I really like it.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "What do you think of America?", "qSentId": 880}, {"answer": "In Germany, definitely, yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "In the modern era, in the last sort of 30, 40 years?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "More designing.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 915, "question": "What's next for the Heidi Klum Incorporated machine?", "qSentId": 914}, {"answer": "From the things -- yes, that I cook up.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 921, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 920}, {"answer": "I would not push them.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 935, "question": "-- to, any of them, to get into fashion, would you worry about it, given the experiences you've had?", "qSentId": 934}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 944, "question": "-- a rock star like their dad?", "qSentId": 943}, {"answer": "Oh, they're a lot of fun.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 955, "question": "Well I -- I look forward to these kids growing up, actually, because they must -- they're going to look great and be very talented, aren't they?", "qSentId": 954}, {"answer": "Oh, my family for sure.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 961, "question": "What's your proudest achievement, you personally?", "qSentId": 960}, {"answer": "And you come home to a guy who just gets on bended knee in igloos and sings you crazy.", "docId": "111119pmt", "aSentId": 969, "question": "And then what?", "qSentId": 968}]